uopxinternational.com 2009-05-03

# Dragon Media Online, Inc.

## Web Privacy Statement

Dragon Media Online ("DMO") and our affiliated companies worldwide are committed to respecting your online privacy and recognize your need for appropriate protection and management of any information you share with us by using our web sites. DMO reserves the right to append or otherwise modify this Privacy Statement at any time, so please re-visit this page occasionally to check for updates. 

DMO has established the following Online Privacy Policy so that you can understand the care with which we intend to treat your information. This policy describes the overall privacy practices of DMO regarding information we collect on our network of web sites and through our other Internet advertising mediums, including but not limited to email. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that DMO does not own or control, or to people that DMO does not employ. 

### Information Collected by DMO

Non-Personally Identifiable Consumer Information

DMO collects various types of information from you to better meet your needs and to provide you with a more relevant user experience. Some of this information is collected automatically through cookies (a small text file placed on your computer) or other Internet tracking technologies. 

### Information Collected Automatically

The types of information your browser or internet session automatically sends us each time you visit one of our sites, which we automatically collect, includes:

  * Your browser, e.g., Internet Explorer, Netscape Navigator.
  * Your Internet domain, e.g., AOL, Netcom, Earthlink, etc.
  * You computer's operating system, e.g., Windows, Macintosh, UNIX, Linux
  * Your navigation path, i.e., the URLs of where you come to our site from, which of our pages you visit, and where you go as your leave.
  * Your IP Address.

This information lets us see how users are finding our sites, and it tells us which pages are visited the most often so we can make our web sites more useful. DMO may also contract with reputable third-party advertising companies to serve ads on our behalf. These companies may also use cookies or other measures to collect your non-personally identifiable information. 

### Personally Identifiable Consumer Information

You may choose whether or not to provide Personal Information to DMO. The notice we intend to provide where DMO collects Personal Information on the Web should help you to make this choice. If you choose not to provide the Personal Information we request, you can still visit most of DMO's Web sites, but you may be unable to access certain options, offers, and services that involve our interaction with you. Examples of personally identifiable data that you may provide to us include name, address, and email address. If you provide personally identifiable data to us, you may later elect to have your information deleted from our files, or kept from being used for purposes other than for the service requested, by following the opt-out procedures set forth below. 

### How Collected Information is Used

The non-personally identifiable information that DMO collects is used for marketing and sales efforts to better target advertisements and other content in an effort to create a more personally relevant experience. The information is also used to predict responses to advertisements, and to help determine which ads perform best and which content is most appropriate for different individuals. 

If you elect to provide DMO with personally identifiable information, we may utilize such information for marketing purposes, and this use may result in follow-up communications from DMO and from our clients. In addition, that information may be combined with information collected from other sources to assist with targeting ads to your preferences and behaviors, and for other DMO sales and marketing efforts. 

### Sharing Information with Third Parties

All personally identifiable information you provide is maintained in confidence by DMO. There are instances, however, in which your personally identifiable and non-personally identifiable information is shared with third parties, as described below. 

Your non-personally identifiable data may be shared with third-party partners of DMO on an anonymous basis. 

When you request information from DMO we may transfer that information within DMO or route your information to the designated party, across borders and from your country or jurisdiction to other countries or jurisdictions around the world, so that they may provide the information on the program that you requested. 

We may also disclose information to a third party who provides programs, products, information or services, which we believe that visitors or users may be interested in purchasing or receiving. In such situations, we will provide you with an opportunity to opt-out of such sharing. Please be aware that DMO is very careful in selecting companies with whom it does business. 

In addition to the above situations where your information may be shared with others, there is also the possibility that DMO, or part(s) of the company, may one day be purchased by, or merged with, another company. In the event of such transaction, the acquiring (or merging) company will have access to all collected personally identifiable information. 

Finally, DMO may share your information as necessary to comply with a court order or to cooperate with government and law enforcement officials. 

### Security

Wherever your personally identifiable information may be held within DMO or on its behalf, we intend to take reasonable and appropriate steps to protect the information you shared with us from unauthorized access or disclosure. Please note that while DMO will make every reasonable effort to protect your information, no transmission of data over the Internet is 100% secure. 

### Non-Personally Identifiable Consumer Information - Use of Cookies & Opting-Out

Some of our web sites utilize cookies to collect information about your website activities and to recall the personal information you previously shared with us. Most browsers allow you to control cookies, including whether or not to accept them and how to remove them. 

You may set most browsers to notify you if you receive a cookie, or you may choose to block cookies with your browser. Blocking cookies may result in a lower quality experience for you while you are visiting DMO web sites. 

### Personally Identifiable Consumer Information - Opting-Out

You may choose whether or not to provide personally identifiable information to DMO. If you choose to provide such information to DMO, you have the right to tell us not to make some of the uses of such information described herein or may have such information deleted in its entirety. If you no longer wish to receive DMO newsletters, surveys or promotional communications via email, you may opt-out by simply contacting us at [privacy@dmoglobal.com](mailto:privacy@dragonmediaonline.com) and provide the name of the service for which information was provided, your full name, mailing address, phone number and email address so that we may identify you in the opt-out process. Once we receive your instruction, we will promptly take corrective action. 

### Access/Accuracy

To the extent that you do provide us with personally identifiable information, DMO wishes to maintain the accuracy of this information. Where we collect personally identifiable information from you on the Web, our goal is to provide a means of contacting DMO should you need to update or correct that information. If for any reason those means are unavailable or inaccessible, you may send updates and corrections about your personally identifiable information to [privacy@dmoglobal.com](mailto:privacy@dragonmediaonline.com) and we will make reasonable efforts to incorporate the changes in the information that we hold as soon as practicable. 

### Children's Privacy

In compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA), DMO is not structured to attract children. Accordingly, we do not intend to collect personally identifiable information from anyone we know to be under 13 years of age. 

### Refer a Friend

Some of DMO's web sites offer you the opportunity to easily notify a friend of the offer or information promoted on the site. If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about a DMO site, we will ask you for your friend's personally identifiable information, including name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. DMO stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program. 

Your friend may contact us at [privacy@dmoglobal.com](mailto:privacy@dragonmediaonline.com) to request that we remove this information from our database. Our one-time email to your friend will inform him or her of this fact. 

### Commitment

Protecting your privacy online is an evolving area, and DMO's web sites are constantly changing to meet these demands. 

If you have any comments or questions regarding our Online Privacy Policy, please contact us at [privacy@dmoglobal.com](mailto:privacy@dragonmediaonline.com). While we cannot guarantee privacy perfection, we will address any issue to the best of our abilities as soon as practicable after you bring it to our attention. 

### Your Consent

By using this web site, you consent to the terms of our Online Privacy Policy and to DMO's processing of personally identifiable information for the purposes given above. Should the Online Privacy Policy change, we intend to take every reasonable step to ensure that these changes are brought to your attention by posting all changes prominently on our web site for a reasonable period of time and by amending this privacy policy. 

### Contacting Us

For more information, or if you have questions or concerns regarding DMO's Privacy Policy, you may email us at:   
Privacy  
Dragon Media Online, Inc.  
1901 Harrison Street Suite 1630  
Oakland, CA 94612  

Thank you for visiting our web site. We hope you have a pleasant experience while you are here.
